LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
I'm a soldier - that means I'm
Both a defendant and the judge
I am standing on both ends of the flame
Rounding curves
Overtaking life and death,
I run and fight with false shadows
No matter how many threads of
deception are woven together,
The truth shall illuminate
the face of light
Save your tears for the day
When our pain is far behind
On your feet, come with me
We are soldiers stand or die
Save your fears, take your place
Save them for the judgement day
Fast and free, follow me
Time to make the sacrifice.
We rise or fall
This afternoon, Prime Minister Kayabuki
made an official visit to Dejima Camp,
the residential refugee sector in Kyuushuu.
This was her first visit after announcing the
repeal of the Refugee Special Treatment Act.
Considering the fact that this
decision was made prematurely,
without instituting any supplemental measures,
such as measures to account for the
refugees' loss of support, and whether
Red Paint: DIE!!
Sign: Promising a New Rebirth of Asia.
February 18th, 2004. Japanese Government
they will be granted Japanese citizenship,
the intensification of protest
from refugees is unavoidable.
Nagasaki
Prime Minister Makes Official Visit to Refugees' "Dejima Camp"
We will now turn to business news.
According to an earlier report...
Refugee Liberation Organisation
Revenge
Samurai
Those
With a
Motive
Here is a copy of the note found in the bouquet that
the Prime Minister received during her official visit.
The forensics results aren't in yet,
but they told us not to expect any
fingerprints or other personal traces.
Refugee Liberation
A threat hinting at the possible
assassination of the Prime Minister?
What about these characters?
We don't know.
We thought you might know something about it.
As far as I can tell, it seems to be
some sort of logo for the organisation.
Ah, yes. Pertaining to the instances of terrorism that
occurred after the takeover of the Chinese Embassy,
the National Police Agency alone has found seven
claims of responsibility bearing that symbol.
Now we've found this assassination threat,
along with a threat against the Nanyou
News Agency, in addition to those seven.
What connections are there
among those nine incidents?
None has been found thus far.
There may have been errors in communication among the
Prefectural Police forces handling the individual cases.
However, the motives and ideological
backgrounds of the perpetrators differ slightly,
not to mention the fact that all of the threats
implied that the would-be terrorist was working alone.
We've just now noticed the
prevalence of this symbol,
and have hastily designated this chain of events
as a major wide-area case.
What of the possibility that some of
the others might have been committed
by copycats mimicking the original for personal
reasons, or simply wishing to stir up the public?
That is impossible to believe,
Even within the police force,
only a select few know about that symbol,
and we haven't told the media about it, either.
If that is true, then the remaining possibilities
include a single group instigating the series
of terrorist attacks and disguising itself by
using individual, unrelated perpetrators...
Or, a Laughing Man-type case in which the individuals
are using some kind of information as a medium.
Well, either way, it's not in our best interest to have the
Prime Minister prevented from carrying out her obligations.
How is the Prime Minister?
That was just a ruse to fool the media.
The Prime Minister wishes to prevent the
media from finding out about the threat.
This is where you and your men come in.
You mean, you want Section 9
to guard the Prime Minister?
You are perceptive.
Commissioner-General, could we have
the original threatening document?
We will be in charge of finding the perpetrator.
Concentrate on guarding the Prime Minister.
Exercise discretion; the media
must not get wind of this.
Major, we will rendezvous at
the Prime Minister's residence.
In other words, they're telling
us to babysit the Prime Minister.
So, what are your thoughts on this case, Chief?
We can't really shrug it off as a group
of copycat criminals flocking to a fad.
The warning basically denounced the Prime Minister for
having repealed the Refugee Special Treatment Act,
which was temporary legislation
promulgated by the previous regime.
After demanding that the Prime Minister put an
end to discrimination and release the refugees,
the author labelled the Prime Minister a traitor
to the people for not solving the refugee problem,
and stated he'd carry out her execution, right?
What he says doesn't make any sense!
Even if this series of events has been
carried out by the same organisation...
it just doesn't seem to hit the mark.
Other than the fact that the same
mark has been used, I see your point.
Although we can't believe everything
the Police Commissioner-General said,
insofar as multiple claims of
responsibility bearing this mark exist,
we must take the possibility into account.
Stand Alone Complex...
This case does share certain similarities
with the Laughing Man case...
Our current objective is not to
speculate on what lies behind the case.
Focus all of your efforts on
guarding the Prime Minister.
However, we will simultaneously conduct an
investigation of the warnings and the symbol,
to try to identify the organisation or
the perpetrator behind these incidents.
Batou, Saitou, and Pazu; you will come
with me to guard the Prime Minister.
Togusa, work on investigating the warning
and the mark with Ishikawa and Bomer.
Roger.
Yesterday, Prime Minister Kayabuki took a
respite from her responsibilities,
but she looked well today and convened
an extraordinary cabinet meeting.
Nonetheless, now that a budget committee
is set to convene in a few days,
without any progress on the
outstanding refugee treatment issue,
Japan's first female Prime Minister
has already lost the
Headlines: Explanation for Visit - Increased Doubts Over Repeals Effectiveness
Nanyou News Agency - Official Visit to Refugee Residential Sector
3,000,000 Refugees Nationwide, Where Will They Go?
Visit to Refugee Camp - First Visit Since Repeal Became Official
initial momentum she had when
the new cabinet was launched.
She seems to be troubled of late...
So, she has not responded to the warning.
Despite having claimed that you'd liberate the
refugees, you show no sign of taking any steps.
It seems the burden of pursuing your
ideals was too great for you to bear.
I will give you greater impetus by
imposing an appropriate sanction.
However...
I will only have one chance to see her in secret.
Now that I've risen, I cannot withdraw
until I have carried out my purpose.
If you rise without purpose,
your ideals will suffer defeat,
no matter what they may be,
and you will fall.
I am one with a motive...
The Individual Eleven.
So, there are now eight incidents in all...
You don't have to do that, Sir.
You caught me at a bad time.
But I do this because I like it.
Headline: Threat Sent to Nanyou News Agency
By acquiring textual information,
I am reinforcing my memory so that the most effective
information will come to mind at the crucial moment.
Well?
Information from the Secretariat, Sir.
Ah.
I see.
A strange new element has been introduced.
Assassination of the Prime Minister? How audacious.
Any idea as to what kind of person he is?
The police have
yet to determine his identity.
I am not surprised.
Who is guarding the Prime Minister?
It appears that Section 9 is in charge.
Section 9, eh?
Well, they shouldn't have any problems.
It wouldn't do to have her
actually assassinated, after all.
All right, have one of our men keep
an eye on the Prime Minister as well.
Get visual confirmation of
the one who made the warning.
If he seems about to fall into Section 9's hands.
let's take steps so that he'll come to us instead.
Understood.
Major, you don't seem really gung-ho about this.
I don't? Must be because I'm having my period.
Come on, cut the jokes.
You know, about the missions
we've been getting lately...
We're supposed to be an organisation
that takes the offensive.
Even though it's true that the
Prime Minister has been threatened,
it's not much fun to be tied down like this.
Are you getting sick of it?
Well, I'm asking you if you feel that way!
I wonder.
None of the previous organisations that were part of the
Refugee Liberation Organisation have used this symbol.
Besides, who knows what these
characters actually say.
You'd think they'd at least have a
legible name for their organisation.
Refugee Liberation Organisation
Revenge
Samurai
"Revenge", the infinity symbol, and "samurai"...
It does seem to imply some sort
of ideological background, but...
It could be that it's just
utilising existing motifs...
As in?
Hmm, let me think...
For example, works of literature by
influential figures in the past...
titles of plays and movies...
and trademarks representing individuals
and organisations in historical events...
I see.
Yup, found it.
This symbol is apparently read,
"The Individual Eleven."
It seems to be the title of a collection of
theories on revolution written half a century ago.
Put it on this screen.
Document Title: "Nations and Revolutions A Detailed Examination
- A Collection of Preliminary Theories on Revolution by Patrick Sylvestre"
It was written by Patrick Sylvestre.
The title is "Nations and Revolutions A Detailed Examination
- A Collection of Preliminary Theories on Revolution."
I've read this before.
A collection of theories on revolution?
At the time, the work wasn't
considered particularly noteworthy.
"The Rise of the Third Estate,"
"The Departure from Domination,"
"The End of Imperial Dynasties,"
"The Search for Socialism,"
"The Night before Rapture,"
"Separation from God,"
"Castro and Guevara,"
"Twelve Years of Nihilism,"
"Return to Principle,"
and "The May Revolution," the actual
revolution which he personally experienced
and which sparked his dream of
becoming the leader of a revolution.
These ten articles comprise this collection
of his early theories on revolution.
However, there is a theory that an
unpublished eleventh article also exists,
and that got shelved because the author
felt that the incident discussed,
which occurred in Japan, was not a revolution.
That mysterious article appears to have
been titled "The Individual Eleven."
But there is no evidence that
the article was ever published.
Yeah. Even this information is basically just
a theory that was espoused by certain obsessive
fans of the author and posted on the net.
What we can't dismiss is the fact that these
obsessive fans are all zealous particularists.
So, a scripture for the individualists...
Now I remember!
This symbol...
Remember when the GSDF helicopter went out of
control and we investigated the dead pilot's home?
Yeah.
I saw a memo with this symbol on it in his room.
Refugee Liberation Organisation
Plus, if I recall correctly, didn't the ones who
occupied the Chinese Embassy also name themselves...
the Individual Eleven.
Headline: Terrorists Name Themselves "The Individual Eleven"
"Individual Eleven"
Major!
I see. That's very interesting,
but that alone won't lead to
the identity of the perpetrator.
Besides, I'm sure the police know that much.
Dig deeper - I don't care how small the leads are.
Find something that will clinch
the identity of the perpetrator.
Understood.
Please check the box's contents.
A message from a comrade who has awakened...
Think over its meaning.
The scripture of my struggle,
"The Individual Eleven"...
Why is it a great work?
That is because he discussed the true nature of the
515 Incident in Japan by contrasting it with Noh.
Note: Noh is traditional Japanese Theatre
Noh was the only art accepted by
samurai during the Warring States Era
when they scorned performance arts in general.
While most performance arts were merely
repetitions of predetermined acts,
Noh theatre alone designated each
performance as a singular event.
They respected Noh because the mental
processes invested in the performance were
considered to be very similar
to those involved in reality.
If one were to end one's singular
existence as the leader of a revolution,
one's life would be elevated to the sublime.
Death brings closure to the hero's
life and gives birth to eternity.
This is what Sylvestre wrote
in "The Individual Eleven."
I'll suggest that to them.
Understood.
Chief Aramaki.
About tomorrow's schedule...
There is no need for any concern.
We will escort you in such a way that
our presence will be unobtrusive.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to ask this of you
when it's a personal affair...
Come in.
Chief.
What is it?
This was apparently delivered along with letters and
packages that were addressed to the Prime Minister.
What is it?
I believe it would be best if
you don't see what's inside.
Unnecessary concern will lead
to discrimination against women.
It's no good.
I can't find anything on the
actual content of the article
What about the incident that was
said to be discussed in the article?
On May 15th, 1932, youth officers from the
Navy, who were caught up in the middle
of a national reorganisation movement,
officer candidates from the Army,
and farmers rose in rebellion.
The leaders assassinated the then Prime Minister.
As a result, Japan was thrust
into an era of military control.
Well, there is no doubt that the officers
committed heinous acts of terrorism,
but the phenomenon that followed the incidents
symbolises the entire affair's significance.
After the Prime Minister's assassination,
the eleven youth officers from the Army who had
participated in the rebellion
were tried in military court.
Their trial began to move in a strange direction.
These youths, who had just turned 20,
refused legal defence on the basis of their
beliefs, prepared themselves for a death sentence,
and tearfully began to give their statements.
And then, the judge, the military officers in
the prosecution, the press, and the spectators
empathised with them and also began to cry.
Furthermore, a commutation movement,
which only began to form near the end of the trial,
became a mass movement after the closing arguments.
By September 19th,
when the verdict was handed down,
there were 350,000 petitions.
And by some strange twist of fate, eleven severed
fingers, the same number as that of the defendants,
were brought into the court room.
Public opinion, which had been leaning toward
ultranationalism, had apparently reached a peak.
After the Prime Minister was assassinated
by these eleven youth officers,
there was a resurgence in nationalism
that glorified them as heroes.
The article was left by an author who
was entranced by this chain of events.
I have a feeling that the author must have strongly
identified with the defendants as he was writing the article.
May Revolution
Refugee Liberation Organisation
They're not real.
These must have been severed from
discarded cybernetic body parts.
Togusa, eleven severed fingers were
delivered to the Prime Minister's Residence.
Find out where these come from.
Eleven... fingers?!
Major, we were continuing with
our investigation of the article,
and we just found details from the 515
Incident that involved eleven severed fingers.
There's something here.
I'm glad it arrived in time.
Many of the devotees who come
here treasure that painting.
That's good.
Hey, hey, so Zen meditation is more significant
as a means of freeing one's karma from
worldly thoughts than as a religion, right?
For us, maybe that's equivalent to
deleting accumulated data in our cache.
And add synchronisation to that, maybe.
Then, if we connect to people in Zen
meditation, maybe we can download enlightenment!
Yeah!
The situation is normal around here.
In any case, what a selfish Prime Minister.
She's being targeted and she wants to
do Zen meditation? What's up with that?
Not to mention that we can't enter the main building...
We can't be held responsible if anything happens.
In her own way, maybe she
understands the situation she's in.
She wanted to practise Zen meditation
precisely because she's in this predicament.
That's why she acquiesced to the unofficial
use of visual interceptors, right?
Well, I respect her courage,
but if you're the only one
who's getting the data feed...
Justice is with me.
Elimination!
It's useless.
You're surrounded.
Tachikoma!
I'm fine.
That was a heavily augmented cyborg.
Start off by investigating military personnel.
I'm sorry.
If you and your team weren't
here, I would've been...
I wonder.
Perhaps it was just that he
didn't really mean to kill you.
Finding out a galaxy
of planets and stars within me.
Listening to each of them
and singing the same silent melody.
I've never seen such beauty
in possibility...
No smack of doubt or fear.
(Wake up)
I hear a voice.
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside
(Our time is now)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
All I need,
to make all this reality.
(it's inside)
The beauty within the shell.
(deep within the shell)
(within the shell)
(Wake up)
I hear a voice
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
(the time is now)
I see inside,
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
to make all this reality,
it's inside
right here within the shell.